Guide to the Stanford University, Feminist Studies Program, honors theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Feminist Studies Program, honors theses
1988-2009
SC4-3443
Stanford University. Feminist Studies Program.
1 Linear feet (17 volumes in 2 boxes)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Feminist Studies Program at Stanford University
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Information about Access
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Feminist Studies Program at Stanford University
Access Terms
Feminist theory--Study and teaching (Higher).; Student papers.; Women's studies.
Collection Contents
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Gallagher, Shamala, The story of Chantel and everybody in her head: a work of fiction in three parts., 2007 (Box 1)
  - Kim, Janet Hyojeong, Heritability: a novel., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Momaya, Masum, Taking her place in the global economy., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Rasch, Meehan, Nothing if not a paradox: incongruity and tension in the early autobiographical writing of May Sarton., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Reinhold, Susan M., Her legitimate mission: debates on abortion, conflicting visions of the world, and the consolidation of liberal democracy in post-revolutionary Portugal., 1988 (Box 1)
  - Rodriguez-SackByrne, Camellia, The woman says "God bless": Irish women speak out on the role of the Catholic Church in their lives., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Rosenbaum, Lisa, Mother's days: stories about mothers and daughters., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Walker, Scott P., Historical relations: the critical project and critical representation of Harriet Taylor and John Stuart Mill., 1991 (Box 2)
  - Glenn, Shenly D., Ada goes to New Zealand!., 1996 (Box 2)
  - Tanenbaum, Molly, Becoming a woman: gender, space and identity in Tetecala, Mexico., 2003 (Box 2)
  - Howton, Elizabeth, The "Lasuens": academic women at Stanford, 1920-1946., 1991 (Box 2)
  - Albright, Kecia, Grassroots mobilization in a Brazilian Favela: gender, consciousness and community in Saõ José., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Frazee, David, Civil rights remedies for gender-motivated violence., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Sword, Kirsten, Nineteenth century health reform: self-control as a social panacea., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Buscho, Sasha, A changing course? Michelle Bachelet and the protress of women's rights in Chile, 1973-2007. (Box 2)
  - Chang, Emily, The more things change, the more they remain the same: the intersection between women's music and women in country and folk music., 1995 (Box 2)
  - Boas, Heidi, Achieving holistic health: the health status of refugee women in Kenya and strategies for change., 2002 (Box 2)